(Howard:)You're in a good mood.
(Sheldon:)Well, it's a new day.
I have a new outlook.
(Sheldon:)You know, I realized
I don't need to worry
(Sheldon:)about other people.
(Sheldon:)I just need to think
more about myself.
(Leonard:)Oh, how will we ever
get used to the new you?
(Raj:)Well, I'm glad to
see you moving forward.
(Sheldon:)Bert did quality
research.
(Sheldon:)And he deserves whatever
accolades he receives.
(Howard:)What is going on?
(Howard:)Did you upgrade
his software last night?
(Leonard:)I think he might be
learning on his own.
(Raj:)Then the robot uprising
has begun.
(Sheldon:)Excuse me, I need to pay Bert
(Sheldon:)a proper congratulations.
(Raj:)He doesn't just look
like C-3PO,
(Raj:)now he walks like him.
(Sheldon:)Bert?
(Sheldon:)I wanted to let you know
that I read your research,
(Sheldon:)and your award is
well-deserved.
(Bert:)Thanks. I've been
hearing that a lot.